Narrator: 1
Speaker: We’ve decided to go to France for our holiday.
Narrator: 2
Speaker: Don’t forget to turn off all the lights.
Narrator: 3
Speaker: We hope to see you again soon.
Narrator: 4
Speaker: I’m learning to drive.
My test is next month.
Narrator: 5
Speaker: I need to go to the supermarket.
I don’t have any milk.
Narrator: 6
Speaker: He offered to help me with my CV.
Narrator: 7
Speaker: They’re planning to get married this summer.
Narrator: 8
Speaker: He pretended to be ill, but he wasn’t really.
Narrator: 9
Speaker: He’s promised to pay me back when he gets a job.
Narrator: 10
Speaker: Remember to bring your dictionaries to class tomorrow.
Narrator: 11
Speaker: It was very cloudy and it started to rain.
Narrator: 12
Speaker: I’m trying to find a job, but it’s very hard.
Narrator: 13
Speaker: I want to catch the six o’clock train.
Narrator: 14
Speaker: I’d like to buy a new car next month.